# **Huda Roushdy**

# Software Engineer

in https://www.linkedin.com/in/huda-roushdy-87362a228/ https://github.com/HodaRoushdy

**G** https://portfolio-brown-sigma-67.vercel.app/

# PROFILE

Experienced web developer trained in React, Nodejs and sql / noSQL database. I have strong problem-solving skills and attention to detail, Ability to collaborate effectively with crossfunctional teams, Excellent communication and teamwork skills, and Hands-on experience with JavaScript Development on both client and server-side

# SKILLS

- ReactS / NEXT.IS
- NodeJS/ Nest.js
- Angular.is +2
- mongoDB
- MySQL / SQLServer / PostgreSQl
- REST API's
- javascript
- typescript
- · Git / GitFlow
- · React-Native
- Mongoose / Sequelize / TypeORM
- html, css, sass & jQuery
- bootstrap / MUI

# **EDUCATION**

# Bachelor's Degree of Computer Science, **Helwan University**

September 2019 – June 2023 3.37 GPA

# Web development Diploma, **Route IT Training Center**

January 2021 – January 2022

# PROJECTS

#### Coligo Platform

School platform using React, Redux, i18n, MUI, unit tests and integration tests

https://coligo-platform.vercel.app/ ≥

#### Coligo Nodejs

provides web services to retrieve all data and make CRUD operations using NodeJs and mongoose

https://coligo-nodejs.vercel.app/ ⊘

#### The Cappa

responsive UI design using html , css and js https://the-cappa-eight.vercel.app/ ⊘

#### Monkey-Pox detector

cross platform application that take an image and describe if it diseased or not using Reactjs

https://monkey-pox-detector.vercel.app/ ∂



#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

### iSchool, Computer Science Instructor

December 2023 – present part time

#### Code Casa.

### Web Developer and Designer internship

October 2023 – November 2023

#### DataCamp, Database Administrator internship

August 2020 – October 2020

#### Freelancer

March 2022 – present



# Supervised Learning with scikit-learn, **DataCamp**

April 2022 – May 2022 | remotely

# **Wedding Company**

#### responsive UI design using html,css and js

https://wedding-company.vercel.app/ ≥

#### Tic-Tac-Toe

#### tic-tac-toe game using NextJs

https://tic-tac-toe-gilt-three.vercel.app/ ⊘

#### Todo List

# Add tasks and mark it as done and delete it easily using React

https://todo-list-react-dun-sigma.vercel.app/ ⊘

# **Bakery**

### responsive UI design using html,css and js

https://bakery-jade.vercel.app/ ⊘

#### **Fokir**

#### responsive UI design using html,css and js

https://fokir-ten.vercel.app/ ⊘

#### **Dashboard**

### dashboard application using Angular

https://angular-task-olive.vercel.app/ ≥